♪ Oh, Mister Tailor ♪
["Mamang Sastre" playing]
- ♪ Fix this ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mister Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors
Oh, Mister Tailor ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Samir, in English] Surprised to see me?
Turns out you wronged both me and Samir.
Where are my children?
You won't see them again.
[Atoy] Now I'll finish you.
You're only brave because you
have many people with you.
[grunting, growling, groaning]
‪PREVIOUSLY
[Viktor, in English]
I am looking for Atoy Padua.
[in English] He owes me plenty!
[Martina, in English] This is…
Tonet and her brother.
Madame, maybe you're being haunted.
That's the one you took out
at the mall, right?
[music swells]
[Emerson] You animals, all of you.
[grunting and groaning]
[Janine] I'm hungry.
That has sleeping pills.
- Huh?
- They want us to fall asleep,
so they can transfer us to the ship.
[grunting and groaning]
[grunts]
- [Gavin] Where's Atoy?
- [Karla] He left. Why?
[Gavin] Someone saw him here.
[in English] She is not Princess.
[man] Who are you?!
What are you doing here?
[grunting and groaning]
‪[grunts]
[Viktor, in English] Who are you?
[in English] You were with Atoy.
[in English] Where is he?
[groaning]
- [gunshots]
- [screaming and panicking]
- [electricity crackling]
- [gunshots]
- [grunts and groans]
[in English] Yes! Security is breached.
- [grunts]
- [gunshots]
[music swells]
- [groans]
- I'm going to kill you!
- [grunts]
- You killed my sister!
- [Karla, in English] No! Let go
- [gunshot]
- [Martina gasps]
- [Red] Atoy is here.
I'm sure he's got company.
- Tatoy!
- [Atoy] Child?
Ibyang!
[music fades]
[in English] Stop! Don't move!
[in English] You are all under arrest!
[pensive music playing]
[in English] You cannot arrest me.
[in English] I have diplomatic immunity!
[in English] Your president
has waived your immunity.
[in English] We can arrest you!
[officer, in English] Men, arrest them!
[grunts, in English] No! No, no, no!
- [grunts]
- [tense music playing]
[in English] You can't do this! [grunts]
[in English] Men, move!
[suspenseful music playing]
- Ibyang.
- Tatoy!
Don't move.
[suave theme music playing]
[in English] Ma'am, please stay behind.
Okay. Thank you.
[somber music playing]
[Janine, in English] Mommy!
- [heavy music playing]
- Janine?
[gasps] Child!
[in English] Mommy.
[sobs]
[in English] Thank God you're okay, child.
[melodramatic music playing]
[Audrey sobs]
Child… [sobs]
Where is Ibyang?
Eh, I don't know where Ibyang is.
I even misled the bad guys earlier
so she could escape.
Where is Ibyang, Mommy?
[sharp inhale]
We'll find her, child. Okay?
[music fades]
Let my child go.
Face me.
You're something else, Atoy, huh?
You even found us here.
You're a skilled tracker, Master Cutter.
But you've cornered me now.
So, we all go down together.
I'll start with your child.
Don't involve my child!
You involved my child!
[dramatic sting]
You brought him here, didn't you?!
He came here because of your viciousness.
[Atoy] He wants to stop you!
So don't project your immorality
and your sins on me.
Fine, fine.
I'm the worst!
It's all my fault!
[ominous music playing]
So, just accept
that we all go down together.
She goes first.
No, Ibyang.
Don't move, Ibyang.
[Atoy sighs]
Red, don't involve my child.
Fine, fine.
I'm the one you want, right?
I'm the one you hate, right?
Fine, take me instead.
I'll go with you.
I'll do everything you want.
I won't resist.
Fine. Take me.
[heavy breath]
- [Atoy] Huh?
- You're brave, fine.
You jump first.
- Fine, fine.
- [Red] Hurry!
Tatoy, don't!
Don't stop him!
He's sacrificing his life for you, right?
Don't you want that? You'll live?
Although your Tatoy dies!
[sobs] No!
It should be you,
because you're the bad one!
You know, my daughter is right.
You're the one who should be eradicated,
because of your savagery!
Then I'll go all out with my savagery.
Tatoy!
[foreboding music playing]
[dagger swishes]
[music swells]
[Ibyang] Tatoy!
[tense music playing]
[squeals]
[music continues]
[gasps]
Karla, Karla, wait.
Stay here first. Okay? I'll help.
No.
They told you to stay here, right?
You've already been shot.
No, I'll help.
It's just a graze.
You're really stubborn, huh?
Gavin, you don't know anything
about gunfights.
Do you really want to die?
Karla…
I'm alive.
Yes, but you almost died.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you because
you're important to me, Gavin.
Why are you telling me that?
You already have a boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend.
Uno is not my boyfriend.
I only said that to make you jealous.
Because the truth is,
you're the one I really like.
I like you, Gavin.
["Sa Wala" instrumental music playing]
Really?
Say it again.
I just want to be sure.
Yes. I like you.
You're the only one who doesn't like me.
No.
I've liked you for a long time, Karla.
Sorry if…
I realized too late
that you're the one I want.
Even when I was with Cathy,
you were the one I was looking for.
No takebacks, okay.
[soft chuckle]
I'll really punch you.
[in English] Final answer.
I'm sure about you.
[chuckles softly]
♪ If this is just for nothing ♪
♪ No more fooling around… ♪
[groans] Ouch, ouch.
[Karla] Oh, are you okay?
♪ The two of us… ♪
It's just a graze.
♪ If this is just for nothing… ♪
[music fades]
[Emerson] It's Audrey! Audrey!
How did you get here?
I've been waiting
at the mainland for a while.
I found out Mercado's men
were going to attack,
so I looked for a way.
Janine, where's Ibyang?
Atoy is probably looking for Ibyang.
[tense music playing]
[Ibyang] Tatoy!
Tatoy!
- Ibyang.
- Tatoy…
[music fades]
[sobs] Tatoy… Don't let go, okay!
[sobs] I'll pinch you!
No!
[sobs] I said don't let go!
Just promise me you'll be good, okay.
[grunts]
Wait a minute.
[sobs] I'll find a way!
Don't let go, okay!
[epic music playing]
Atoy!
- [Uno] Sir Atoy!
- [Kurt] Atoy!
[Uno] Don't let go, okay.
- [Paldo] Sir Atoy!
- Here, here!
- [grunts]
- [epic music playing]
[Kurt] Here!
[Kurt grunts]
[Atoy grunts]
[grunts, then groans]
[pants]
[Atoy groans]
- [soft drama music playing]
- [Ibyang sobs]
[accessories jingling]
[softly] Thank you.
[Atoy, softly] Thank you.
[accessories jingling]
[Ibyang sobs]
My child.
[sobbing]
Good thing you didn't fall.
[sobs] If you did,
I'd really pinch you!
[melodramatic music playing]
Even at your funeral, I'd still scold you!
- [soft chuckle]
- [sobbing]
Good thing. [soft chuckle]
[sobbing]
[Audrey gasps]
Ibyang, child.
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
[music fades]
We're incomplete.
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
- [sentimental music playing]
- [sobbing]
Thank you, Saint Anthony.
[sobbing]
My family is whole again.
[accessories jingling]
[music fades]
[gentle music playing]
We thank everyone for the support
and the cooperation
of all the agencies
involved in this operation.
How did you find out
that the human traffickers could be found
in Velora Bay,
as well as the number one
wanted bagman in the Philippines?
That also includes locating
the concentration camps
of the known terrorist group Obsidian
here in our country.
They say it takes a village
to execute an operation.
But the truth is,
it is all because of one man.
[camera shutter snapping]
[in English] A man
who wanted his family back.
[in English] You can have
all the right reasons to do good,
but family is the strongest force
to do your best.
[female reporter] Who is he?
[in English] May we know his name, sir?
[in English] Is he part of the military?
Where is he now?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] It's classified information,
but I call him…
The Master Cutter.
[music fades]
[action music playing]
[phone ringing]
[Atoy, in English] Are you in position?
- [music fades]
- Copy.
- I'm on my way.
- [phone blips]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Audrey] Where are we going?
[in English] Why did you
make me wear this?
[Janine] Because you look beautiful in it.
[Audrey] Where's your daddy anyway?
Hmm, Tatoy left. He has a mission.
So, what we'll do is just pray
that his mission will be successful.
Yes.
[light music playing]
Daddy is really amazing.
[in English] Wait.
[in English] What's going on?
[Janine] Hmm, just wait.
[pensive music playing]
[sentimental music playing]
- Um…
- [clears throat]
[in English] Wow.
Audrey…
Sorry if
I didn't admit to you at first who I was,
and sorry because when…
when we met again,
I didn't admit to you my true feelings.
But I don't want to be sorry
for not doing this.
Audrey Regalia.
[in English] Will you marry me?
[giggles]
[in English] Yes!
- [exclaiming and cheering]
- [sentimental music playing]
- [in English] Yes.
- [in English] Will you
marry me right now?
- Now?
- [Atoy] Now!
[stutters]
Yes! Now!
[exclaiming and cheering]
[Father Peping]
We are all gathered here today
to witness the union
of our brother Atoy and Audrey
before our Lord
and our patron Saint Anthony of Padua.
[music fades]
[sentimental music playing]
[inaudible]
[Ibyang] The Lord is truly amazing,
because He listened to my prayer.
I thought I would grow up without parents.
I thought I would be alone.
But look, I have Tatoy and Mommy now.
I even have a sister!
I'm so happy with my family.
[in English]
And now, you may kiss the bride.
- [music swells]
- [exclaiming and cheering]
[sentimental music playing]
[all] One more! One more! One more!
[exclaiming and cheering]
[light music playing]
[Ibyang] I'm also happy because
our family got to meet
and be with the people
who helped my Tatoy.
They are the ones who are always there
and care about him.
Even though Tatoy was grumpy back then,
he already considered everyone
from Tabang Lupa as family now.
[inaudible] What?
[Ibyang] Who would have thought that
in the middle of our community
there's a tough tracker,
who's also handsome,
like my Tatoy!
[exclaiming and cheering]
- [sentimental music playing]
- [Ibyang] What could his next mission be?
Who will he look for next?
Whatever it is,
the most important thing
we found was each other.
[exclaiming and cheering]
[laughing and exclaiming]
[lively chattering]
[Ibyang] So, thank you, Papa Jesus.
Thank you also, Saint Anthony of Padua,
for my family.
Especially for Master Grumpy.
Just kidding!
Thank you to my Tatoy.
The best Master Cutter!
- [man] One, two, three! Cheese!
- One more!
- [camera shutter snaps]
- There!
[exclaims and giggles]
- [camera shutter snaps]
- [in English] Okay!
- [exclaiming]
- [lively chattering]
- Wait. Hold on, hold on.
- [phone ringing]
- [man] You saw Brother Kurt earlier!
- Excuse me. Excuse me, okay.
- [lively chattering]
- [Atoy, in English] Hello, sir?
Oh? You called?
[Mercado on the phone, in English]
Padua, I know you're on leave,
but I just had to let you know.
Samir escaped just this morning
from the hospital
before he was transferred to prison.
You should still be careful.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[electronic blipping]
♪ Oh, Mister Tailor ♪
["Mamang Sastre" playing]
♪ Fix this ♪
♪ Wait a moment, Mister Tailor ♪
♪ Can you be the one to sew ♪
♪ My polo's hole that fits
Just under the armpit ♪
♪ Sleeves too long, buttons gone ♪
♪ Like a flood control project
And budget ♪
♪ That vanished like a bubble ♪
♪ Your table's a mess
But your eyes are clear ♪
♪ You're too sharp, you see everything ♪
♪ Measured exactly, back to front ♪
♪ You know what's off and what's right ♪
♪ You're too sharp, you see everything ♪
♪ Everything's measured exactly ♪
♪ In every cut of cloth ♪
♪ There's a secret behind it ♪
♪ If your measurement is wrong
The whole fit turns crooked ♪
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble ♪
♪ All excuses disappear ♪
♪ Under the light, the trick is seen ♪
♪ There's a cool kid on the corner ♪
♪ Geng-geng, geng-geng-geng right away ♪
♪ Cut it and bring it
To BGC and Parqal precinct ♪
♪ Always using "strategy" as an excuse ♪
♪ If the stitch of the system is wrong
It's always hard to escape ♪
♪ Oh, Master Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, the matter is over ♪
♪ In the city's mess, you're the timing ♪
♪ If you're the one who cuts, it's clean ♪
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble ♪
♪ Promises vanished ♪
♪ In an instant, all gone ♪
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble ♪
♪ Promises vanished ♪
♪ In an instant, all gone ♪
♪ Fix this ♪